He has a question. Well, let me answer the question, right? You keep saying, what about October 7? What about October 10? What about October 8? What about October 9? What about October 10? What about October 11? What about October 12? What about October 13? What about October 14? What about October 15? What about October 16? What about October 17? What about October 18? What about October 19? What about October 20? What about October 21? What about October 22? Let me finish the question. Let me finish answering.
What about October 23rd?
What about October 24th?
What about October 25th?
What about October 26th?
What about October 27th?
What about October 28th?
What about October 29th?
What about October 30th?
What about October 31st?
What about November 1st?
What about November 2nd?
November 23rd?
What about November 5th?
What about November 6th?
What about November 7th?
What about November 8th?
What about November 9th?
What about tomorrow?
What about the next day?
where's your answer
you did really great
good job
we need somebody like you